<game_dialog>

    <dialog dialog_id = "Outdoor Scene">
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>This is ridiculous.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message speed="100">What?</message>
        
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>The whole "no mounts" thing. This trip took us, like, three days.</message>
        <message style="italic" type="append">I don't think my feet even exist anymore.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>Well, what do you want me to do about it? The rules are there for a reason.</message>
        
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>What reason can you think of for us walking across the entire damn provence? </message>
        <message style="italic" type ="append">Tell me, Farrand.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message style="italic">Well, </message>
        <message type="append">for one, horses eat things they're not supposed to. </message>
        <message type="append">They're invasive.</message>
        
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Then we can bring some feed or something. You're a higher up now, </message>
        <message type="append">why don't you bring the issue to a meeting?</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>Oh, so then I can be "Farrand: Patron of Sloth" for the rest of my life. </message>
        <message type="append">Proposing amendments isn't taken lightly, you know.</message>
        
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Well, I guess so. Still... </message>
        <message style="italic" type="append">three days</message>
        <message type="append">, man.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>You shouldn't be calling me </message>
        <message style="italic" type="append">man</message>
        <message type="append">, either. </message>
        <message type="append"> We need to get into the habit of being professional</message>
        <message>if I want to make good first impressions as a sage.</message>

        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Yeah, whatever... What matters now is that we got here.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>Yes. Now let's try to make this go smoothly. Remember: weapons down, </message>
        <message type="append">do not act out, and let me do the talking.</message>
    </dialog>

    <dialog dialog_id="Outdoor Scene p2">
        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>Emphasis on "let me do the talking".</message>
    </dialog>
    
    
    


    <dialog dialog_id="entering_zesilia1">
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Farrand, we have arrived at the Gates of Zeslia.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>Good.</message>
    </dialog>
    <dialog dialog_id="entering_zesilia2">
        <header>Guard</header>
        <message>You there! State you name and business in the city of Zeslia!</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>I am Farrand, Sage of Nuado, and this is Jeremiah.</message>
        <message type="append">We are here on official business to speak with Waldomar II.</message>

        <header>Guard</header>
        <message>You are permitted to enter.</message>
    </dialog>

    <dialog dialog_id="road to waldos house">
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message speed="600">....</message>

        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message speed="39">So... Mighty nice weather we are having today aren't we?</message>

        <header>Guard</header>
        <message>Waldomar has ordered we keep contact to a minimum.</message>

        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Oh ok then...</message>

    </dialog>
    <dialog dialog_id="Waldos meeting">
        <header>Waldomar</header>
        <message>Ah, Farrand, the man of the hour! I was worried you would keep us waiting!</message>
        <message type="append">So, did my little crew here give you a warm welcome?</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>...</message>

        <header>Waldomar</header>
        <message>...Please, make yourself comfortable! </message>
        <message type="append">Want a cigar?</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>No thank you, I’d like to get Straight to the point.</message>

        <header>Waldomar</header>
        <message>Well then, by all means! Tell me, why have we gathered here today?</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>I have come to order the halt of the Adlers' urban expansion project.</message>
        <message type="append">As I am sure you are aware, industrialization poses a threat to both</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <mesage>our environment and to our state of social well-being.</mesage>

        <header>Waldomar</header>
        <message>You have come to “halt me and my expansion”?</message>

        <header>Waldomar</header>
        <message>Why, whatever do you mean by that?</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>You know as well as I do what it means... Your further expansion past</message>
        <message type="append">the **east west line** is a clear violation of the **candidus treaty** that</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>our fathers agreed upon all those years ago.</message>

        <header>Waldomar</header>
        <message>Ah, but Farrand it would be selfish to keep all that land to yourself!</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>What’s selfish is the lavish lifestyle you live while many of your followers </message>
        <message type="append">starve!</message>

        <header>Waldomar</header>
        <message>The state of my own followers is their doing. They are truly free </message>
        <message type="append">to work and live as they please.</message>

        <header>Waldomar</header>
        <message>They don’t have imposed reproduction rights or live in blasted huts </message>
        <message type="append">eating leaves and berries like animals.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>The citizens of Isthmo do not live like animals! They are simply free of the corruption and destruction of mans old ways of living. I know your type Waldomar, your thirst for power is unquenchable, you won’t be satisfied until you have completely stripped this land of all of it’s resources in exchange for material wealth!</message>
        <message type="append">dfskjgshdfk</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>It’s because of people like you in the **old world** that Isthmo Candidus was created as a safe haven from ecological destruction in the first place and I'll be damned if I even let you have an inch more of it!</message>

        <message type="append">BBRRAAEHHEERG</message>


        <header>Waldomar</header>
        <message>I will not idly sit by and take these insults! Guards arrest them on charges of</message>
        <message type="append">treason!</message>



    </dialog>




</game_dialog>
