<game_dialog>
    <dialog dialog_id = "Outdoor Scene Old">
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Farrand, we are about half way to Zeselia,</message>
        <message type="append">we should make it there within the next week.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>Good, Waldomar said this meeting will be peaceful but keep your wits about you, </message>
        <message type="append">I fear he may have bad intentions.</message>

        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Really?</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>Yes, his father was from the old world where man was left unchecked </message>
        <message type="append">and humanity ravaged the world environmentally to the point of no return.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>Isthmo is one of the only habitable areas left on earth that still has </message>
        <message type="append">valuable resources. I wouldn’t be surprised if he tries to take it all for himself.</message>

        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>With an all out war? </message>
        <message type="append">Do they really think they can stand up to us with our advanced magic and the spore thing?.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>We can’t be sure. They too have made progress with their weaponry since</message>
        <message type="append">the last great war ended 20 years ago. Granted, they still use gunpowder.</message>

        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Interesting...</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>But the fact remains that Waldomar II has been encroaching on our land  </message>
        <message type="append">for the past 2 years now and believes we haven’t noticed.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>Our scouts have also reported his troops mobilizing along our borders. </message>

        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>In that case I fear the worst may come of this meeting.</message>
        <message type="append">Are you sure its a good idea?</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>The chance to avoid a second war, however slim it may be, is worth the risk. </message>

        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Good point.</message>

        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>There’s a stream up ahead. We can set up camp for the night there.</message>
    </dialog>
    <dialog dialog_id = "Outdoor Scene">
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>This is ridiculous.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>What?</message>
        
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>The whole "no mounts" thing. This trip took us, like, three days.</message>
        <message style="italic">I don't think my feet even exist anymore.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>Well, what do you want me to do about it? The rules are there for a reason.</message>
        
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>What reason can you think of for us walking across the entire damn provence?</message>
        <message style="italic">Tell me, Farrand.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message style="italic">Well, </message>
        <message>for one, horses eat things they're not supposed to. They're invasive.</message>
        
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Then we can bring some feed or something. You're a higher up now, why don't you bring the issue to a meeting?</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>Oh, so then I can be "Farrand: Patron of Sloth" for the rest of my life. Proposing amendments isn't taken lightly, you know.</message>
        
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Well, I guess so. Still... </message>
        <message style="italic">three days</message>
        <message>, man.</message> 

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>You shouldn't be calling me </message>
        <message style="italic">man</message>
        <message>, either. We need to get into the habit of being professional if I want to make good 
first impressions as a sage.</message>

        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Yeah, whatever... What matters now is that we got here.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>Yes. Now let's try to make this go smoothly. Remember: weapons down, do not act out, and let me do the talking.</message>
        <message type="append">Emphasis on "let me do the talking".</message>

        
    </dialog>
    
    
    


    <dialog dialog_id="entering_zesilia1">
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Farrand, we have arrived at the Gates of Zeslia.</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>Good.</message>
    </dialog>
    <dialog dialog_id="entering_zesilia2">
        <header>Guard</header>
        <message>You there! State you name and business in the city of Zeslia!</message>

        <header>Farrand</header>
        <message>I am Farrand, Sage of Nuado, and this is Jeremiah.</message>
        <message type="append">We are here on official business to speak with Waldomar II.</message>

        <header>Guard</header>
        <message>You are permitted to enter.</message>
    </dialog>

    <dialog dialog_id="road to waldos house">
        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message speed="600">....</message>

        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message speed="39">So... Mighty nice weather we are having today aren't we?</message>

        <header>Guard</header>
        <message>Waldomar has ordered we keep contact to a minimum.</message>

        <header>Jeremiah</header>
        <message>Oh ok then...</message>

    </dialog>




</game_dialog>
